You seem to be making good progress.
I think you're at around 30% now.
Does that mean I can use my powers again?
Not at all.
It means that you'll die if you use 30%
of what used to be your full power.
What?!
Blade.
Oh, what's up?
This is Maria.
She's my friend, and...
Oh, I remember her!
She was in the magic unit when we fought Cu.
Oh, yes...
She tripped all the time during training...
and in the actual fight, I think she hurled
a fireball in the wrong direction...
Hey! Blade!
What do you call people like her, again?
That's right!
A klutz, that was it!
Ah, sorry.
It's fine...
It's true that I'm clumsy.
Um, it seems she has a favor to ask of you.
Me?
Y-Yes.
Blade...
Can you please...
kill me?
Oh, no!
I meant that I want you to kill me
when I lose control of myself.
Episode 5
What do you mean by that?
The Demon King's
Daughter
Um, the truth is... I'm not human.
What?
Yeah, you're a night demon, right?
You can tell?
Well, I had a hunch.
There's something else
that exists inside me.
A magical beast with fearsome powers.
Just once before, when I was
having a very hard time...
Ah!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
This is what happens when
I can't control my strength!
It's okay, Maria.
Take a deep breath.
Until now, I was able to
somehow keep it in check.
But ever since then, I haven't
been able to fully hold it back.
You mean when we fought Cu?
Touching fighting spirit, which flowed
through your magic energy conduits,
made you lose control of your powers.
You mean, unless we do something, that beast
is going to come out and wreak havoc?
Yes.
But I have nowhere else to go if
I get kicked out of the academy.
Maria was originally at
Rosewood Junior School, like I was.
She's worked hard for so
long to enter this academy.
My mother and father are gone.
I don't have a home to go back to.
That's why I need to do
something about these powers!
Sure.
I know what it's like,
since my parents are gone, too.
I'll help you out.
Me, too.
I never knew my mother or father.
I'll help you as well.
Us, too!
And I as well, naturally.
I'm friends with Maria now!
It's only natural to help out a friend!
H-Hey!
I want to help out, too!
Thank you so much, everyone!
A magic barrier?
Whoa, how much power is this?!
Oh, I asked Claire and Yessica to adjust it,
so it should be cranked up to max power.
Yay!
You didn't ask for permission, did you?
All right, looks like we're all set.
You've been holding back
your powers this whole time,
so I thought you could try
releasing them just this once.
No!
I mustn't!
That's why we prepared all this.
Earnest is living proof that it can work.
Well, I suppose.
I can't ever do that!
I must not unleash these powers!
I need to keep them locked up
for the rest of my life...
Maria.
Why don't we try following
Blade's suggestion?
It saved me once before.
It is kind of a stupid method, though.
Don't call it stupid!
What part of it isn't stupid, dummy?!
Shut up, dummy!
I understand.
I'll put my faith in Blade
and the rest of you.
I leave it to you if the worst comes to pass.
Yeah. We've got this.
Okay, here I go.
Each of these limits my power by half.
Another one.
Now it's four times the power.
And another.
Eight times.
Sixteen times?!
And finally...
This is the most powerful sealing item,
restricting my power to one-tenth.
Which means...
One hundred and sixty times.
Wait, Maria!
Huh?
She's...
She's about to come out!
Oh, no! I can't hold her back!
Don't hold back!
We'll take care of her!
Believe in your friends!
Blade, that's...
The Demon King...
Bow before me!
Fear me! Worship me!
Rejoice in the birth of the Demon King
with cries of lament and rancor!
That's the Demon King?
No.
But the satanic crest on her forehead...
Consume my flesh, Asmodeus!
My lord!
How dare you!
Is that all?
Hm?
Artificial Great Hero Power:
Ultimate Gravity.
Oh, I can't move after that.
I leave the rest to you...
Well, then, are you ready?
So hot.
Here.
You can have it back.
Are you the last one left?
Okay.
Once I'm out of here,
I'll lay waste to the royal capital.
What's the meaning of this?
Don't tell me you're trying
to take the Demon King alive?
Found me out?
You're a funny one.
Fight me seriously.
Or I'll kill you.
I'm here to kill you.
If you don't intend to kill me,
I'll make sure you die.
Don't give out on me, body!
Hm?
Is that all you've got?
If so, now it's my turn.
Don't die in one shot now.
Hey, wait!
Sun Ray.
Oh? You're still alive?
Blade.
Earnest! Don't push yourself!
Take this...
Asmodeus.
This goes very much against my will,
but it is what my master desires.
I shall consider this a limited contract.
Oh? Now that's a fine weapon.
It looks like I can expect
a somewhat amusing fight.
Sorry. I don't fight to amuse anyone.
I'll be ending this with one blow.
You think you can take down
the Demon King in one blow?
Interesting!
Show me, then!
S-Stop that!
I'm not sure if even I can
fully handle such power!
Quit your grumbling.
You're Earnest's sword,
so bear it with sheer willpower.
Here I go!
Holy Demon Blade!
Come forth!
Pretty impressive.
Th-This can't be!
I'm being overpowered?!
You!
What the hell are you?!
Just your ordinary fellow.
At least, I am now!
I'm just glad no one ended up dying...
Huh?
I'm...
You idiot!
You big, fat idiot!
You don't have to be so reckless anymore!
Why do you always make me worry so much?!
Um...
You were dead, you know!
If I hadn't gotten to you in time,
you would have been a goner!
Last time, you promised you
wouldn't make me cry again!
You liar!
Sorry.
I'll be careful from now on.
And the others?
They'll be fine.
Claire is treating them as we speak.
I see.
And what about her?
She's alive.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Pretty impressive.
Good morning!
G-Good morning!
Good morning.
Hey, good morning.
Good morning, Great Hero—
So I was right.
Now I have something to use against you.
Stop it, Maria. Seriously.
Maria is a different personality.
Then who are you?
I don't... have a name.
No one's ever given me one.
De-mao!
Good morning, De-mao!
Good morning.
De-mao?
It's true.
I am the one who welcomed
Maria into this school.
I'm aware of her identity.
Maria's mother was human.
Unfortunately, she's passed away.
And her father?
His fate is unknown.
However, we know who he is.
Her father was once known
as the Demon King.
In other words, she's the
Demon King's daughter.
She really has gotten used to life here.
But she's dangerous, right?
Is it okay to leave her alone like this?
Well...
His Majesty decided to let her go free,
saying, "I'll take full responsibility!"
Right now, with my powers curbed,
I'm just an ordinary young girl.
If you tell me to attend school, I'll do so,
and if you tell me to wear this
frilly garb, I will oblige.
You say that, but don't you really
just want to wear cute clothes?
Stop that, Yessica!
Don't make her angry!
Hm.
If I'm honest, it does set my heart aflutter.
This frilly garb is quite something.
Mao!
Let those girls go back to
their classrooms already!
I didn't ask them to come here.
Hey, why are you calling her Mao?
Think of it like a nickname.
Everyone calls her De-mao,
but Mao is shorter.
I see.
Yes. I am almighty, and generous as well.
I will allow this young girl to call me Mao.
Dragons are the almighty ones!
What'd you say, whelp?
Do you want a rematch?
Parent!
That's enough.
Break time is over.
Great— I mean, Blade.
I'd happily welcome a
rematch with you any day.
Now then, let us be off.
Um...
Mao and Maria are distinct
personalities, right?
Yes.
Then how come Maria hasn't
shown herself ever since then?
That's a good point.
I'm scared.
Scared that I'll never be
able to see Maria again.
Good morning, Great Hero Blade.
That's not right!
I see.
I suppose I should say, "Good evening."
Well, what do you want?
Yes. I'm here to invite you.
I heard about it from a fellow classmate.
She called it a da...
Yes, a date!
Huh?
Listen up!
A date begins at 1000 hours...
H-Hey!
Look, Great Hero.
The moons are beautiful tonight.
Seriously, stop calling me that!
Besides, the moons are always out at night!
Maria spent all her time
staring at the ground.
Oh, yeah. How old are you, anyway?
You don't seem to know a whole lot.
I began to gain self-awareness
around five years ago.
Huh? You're five years old?
Age is no matter to a magical beast.
As a lady, however, I don't appreciate
being treated as a child.
You're a lady now?
Can't you see for yourself?
And here I am, so attached to you.
Is that right?
The reason I've stayed at this school
is because of you, Great Hero.
You looked like you were enjoying
life here at the academy.
Yes, there's that, too.
I do enjoy that frilly garb.
However, a magical beast
seeks out strength by nature.
Everything else can be
discarded when it sees fit.
And yet, I'm attached to you,
for reasons I don't fully understand.
Even though you've grown weaker
since our previous fight.
I was told that I'll die if I use
15% of my power next time.
As you are, you're not a
foe worth even killing.
But I've made up my mind.
I won't leave this place
until I've killed you.
Man, that's brutal.
It's not good to be unaware
of your own feelings.
I've thought about it,
and came up with a hypothesis.
That is...
Perhaps I've become attracted to you.
What?!
It's just a hypothesis,
which is why I want to test it out.
Won't you be my mate?
I don't really know what that'd involve...
Neither do I.
You do realize I'm five.
Wouldn't it be easier to
head over to a testing ground,
and fight until we're both satisfied?
You're in no shape to fight.
What's more, I can't take
this off of my own volition.
Maria's consciousness
within me resists it.
She's so weak, yet she defies me...
At the very least, I suppose she
did bring me into this world.
What happened to Maria?
Are Claire and the others worried?
She's hiding away in the
deepest recesses of the mind.
Despite appearances, there are dark
shadows stewing within Maria's heart.
She was scorned and feared by humans...
She rued her misfortune, forced to
live in hiding with only our mother.
Our mother believed in our father.
However, Maria could not have faith in him.
Eventually, our mother died,
and Maria's mind was flooded with doubt.
Could it be that our father
had not loved our mother?
Why had he abandoned the human realm?
Could it be that our father was
the cause of all of her suffering?
I was born in order to escape
that unbearable pain in her mind.
I see...
So perhaps Maria might never return.
It would be easier that way.
I've told you all this because you're
closer to our kind than to humanity.
One more thing I like about you.
That's all in the past now.
A few days later
From my research, I just can't see how
that pendant could be a sealing item!
What?
Um... who is this?
She's Maria's friend...
Eliza!
Are you sure it's not a sealing item?
I'm absolutely certain!
If I'm wrong, I swear to disembowel myself!
You don't have to go that far!
You say that, but I'm definitely
being restricted by this item.
What kind of item is it?
Right.
I haven't been able to fully analyze it,
but I believe that it's some
sort of recording device.
Recording?
You could consider it a type of message cube.
This is just conjecture,
but it may contain a message from
the person who gave you that pendant.
Going by Maria's memories,
this was a keepsake from our mother.
Let me warn you beforehand.
I believe that recording could
serve to bring Maria back.
That would mean...
I see.
It could end up destroying me,
the Demon King.
How fascinating.
Would we be okay if we play it?
Yes, go ahead.
In that case, let us begin.
Perhaps we could have become friends, too.
If it didn't mean losing Maria...
Rest assured.
It seems that one of us
is destined to disappear.
I'm sure whoever remains will
be friends with you all.
I'm ready now.
Please open the pendant.
Yes.
The Demon King.
So this is the Demon King?
Huh, he's pretty hot!
My beloved Emilia.
Emilia?
Our mother's name.
Find it in your heart to forgive
me for leaving you behind...
No, resent me.
There is a foe whom I must face in combat.
I do not wish to take you
down this bloodied path.
You may think it self-serving of me...
but there is a reason I cannot.
You may not have realized it yet,
but your body houses a brand-new life.
To think that I, a magical beast,
could sire a child with a human.
Be it a boy or a girl,
I've chosen names.
Ortous if it is male.
If it is female, Maria.
Once that child can understand language,
tell them this:
Their father is dead.
How long are you going to hide in here for?
It's no fun beating someone
as useless as you.
I'm...
Emilia. My child yet unseen.
I swear upon my satanic crest that
I will continue loving you both.
Forevermore, though my body may perish.
Mao, you're...
Yes.
I can barely control my body now.
It seems that the strength of our wills
plays a role in this battle, too.
As we speak, the two of us are fighting
to see which one gets to survive.
It looks like I'm about to
be annihilated by Maria.
H-Hey...
It's almost time.
Go on, call her name.
I don't mind.
Maria!
Blade!
Don't you lose to her!
Maria! You can do it!
Maria! Show us the usual!
Um... do you mind?
It's fine.
Okay...
Come, Blade!
Your life ends here!
Let's go!
Mao didn't disappear, which means...
It must be because Maria
wants to coexist with her.
This is the future she wanted.
Surrender already!
The Demon King would never...
Mao!
Show Blade who's boss!
Next Time
The General and the Sacred Bird